Jai Hind friends, how are you all? I hope
you are all well. Friends, if you
are a good CSC, then how will you insure a vehicle on your own,
that too in two minutes.
Today we will explain in this video. So first of all,
we will
login to our digital seva portal.
After logging in, we will
go to services and select insurance. We
select insurance.
Many companies are listed. So
today we will select ICC Lombard policy.
Friends, this is a very good portal. We will
enter the vehicle number in it. We will
click on get RTO details. All the
details of the vehicle will come automatically.
After that, click on get court. Let's wait a
little. Friends, see, this is how much
your vehicle insurance will cost. The
complete details have been entered in it and are given below. You
can see them by clicking [music]. After that, we
click on proceed.
Click on chair. We come down and the
details of the entire vehicle are shown.
Friends, stay till the end of the video, you
can make your own insurance and earn a good commission.
Friends, click on the complete option of the vehicle.
[music]
Click on KYC.
Three options are given here, you can use it for PAN card or
Aadhar card. If there is a
PAN card, then by entering the PAN number
and date of birth, we will click on submit
and if there is an Aadhar card, then if there is an
Aadhar number, date of birth and email, we will
click on submit.
After that,
friends, if you like this video, then do
subscribe to the channel
and do not forget to like and share. Friends,
after that we click on submit. There is a
little time delay in getting the data files,
friends, let's
wait a little. See friends, the data
pack is complete. How much has been added in the Aadhar number,
what is the address, everything is complete.
Nothing needs to be done in this, friends, and click on proceed.
We see that all the
customer
information that has to be entered is automatically taken. Let's
click on net profit. Friends,
see, option A will
automatically take you to the payment mode and after
excluding your commission, the money will be deducted from the CSC
and you can pay the customer's PF.
See friends,
maybe it seems that's why you have to do it.
Friends, stay tuned to the video till the end.